<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<filmyDataList>
    <FilmyData>
        <title>Avatar: The Way of Water</title>
        <filmImage>avatar2</filmImage>
        <director>James Cameron</director>
        <writers>James Cameron, Rick Jaffa, Amanda Silver, Shane Salerno, Josh Friedman</writers>
        <cast>Sam Worthington, Zoe Saldaña, Sigourney Weaver, Stephen Lang, Kate Winslet, Cliff
            Curtis
        </cast>
        <language>English</language>
        <country>USA</country>
        <plot>Set more than a decade after the events of the first film, learn the story of the
            Sully family (Jake, Neytiri, and their kids), the trouble that follows them, the lengths
            they go to keep each other safe, the battles they fight to stay alive, and the tragedies
            they endure.
        </plot>
        <genre>Action, Adventure, Fantasy</genre>
    </FilmyData>
    <FilmyData>
        <title>How to Train Your Dragon</title>
        <filmImage>howtotrainyourdrgon1</filmImage>
        <director>Chris Sanders</director>
        <writers>Chris Sanders, Dean DeBlois, Cressida Cowell, William Davies</writers>
        <cast>Jay Baruchel, Gerard Butler, Craig Ferguson, America Ferrera, Jonah Hill, Christopher
            Mintz-Plasse
        </cast>
        <language>English</language>
        <country>USA</country>
        <plot>As the son of a Viking leader on the cusp of manhood, shy Hiccup Horrendous Haddock
            III faces a rite of passage: he must kill a dragon to prove his warrior mettle. But
            after downing a feared dragon, he realizes that he no longer wants to destroy it, and
            instead befriends the beast – which he names Toothless – much to the chagrin of his
            warrior father.
        </plot>
        <genre>Animation, Adventure, Family</genre>
    </FilmyData>
    <FilmyData>
        <title>Despicable Me</title>
        <filmImage>despicableme1</filmImage>
        <director>Pierre Coffin, Chris Renaud</director>
        <writers>Sergio Pablos</writers>
        <cast>Steve Carell, Miranda Cosgrove, Dana Gaier, Elsie Fisher, Jason Segel, Russell Brand
        </cast>
        <language>English</language>
        <country>USA</country>
        <plot>Villainous Gru lives up to his reputation as a despicable, deplorable and downright
            unlikable guy when he hatches a plan to steal the moon from the sky. But he has a tough
            time staying on task after three orphans land in his care.
        </plot>
        <genre>Animation, Comedy, Family</genre>
    </FilmyData>
    <FilmyData>
        <title>Johnny English</title>
        <filmImage>johnyenglish1</filmImage>
        <director>Peter Howitt</director>
        <writers>Neal Purvis, William Davies, Robert Wade</writers>
        <cast>Rowan Atkinson, Natalie Imbruglia, Ben Miller, John Malkovich, Greg Wise</cast>
        <language>English</language>
        <country>USA</country>
        <plot>A lowly pencil pusher working for MI7, Johnny English is suddenly promoted to super
            spy after Agent One is assassinated and every other agent is blown up at his funeral.
            When a billionaire entrepreneur sponsors the exhibition of the Crown Jewels—and the
            valuable gems disappear on the opening night and on English's watch, the
            newly-designated agent must jump into action to find the thief and recover the missing
            gems.
        </plot>
        <genre>Action, Adventure, Comedy</genre>
    </FilmyData>
    <FilmyData>
        <title>Pirates of the Caribbean: The Curse of the Black Pearl</title>
        <filmImage>pirates1</filmImage>
        <director>Gore Verbinski</director>
        <writers>Gore Verbinski, Ted Elliott, Terry Rossio</writers>
        <cast>Johnny Depp, Orlando Bloom, Keira Knightley, Geoffrey Rush, Jack Davenport, Jonathan
            Pryce, Lee Arenberg, Mackenzie Crook
        </cast>
        <language>English</language>
        <country>USA</country>
        <plot>Jack Sparrow, a freewheeling 18th-century pirate, quarrels with a rival pirate bent on
            pillaging Port Royal. When the governor's daughter is kidnapped, Sparrow decides to help
            the girl's love save her.
        </plot>
        <genre>Action, Adventure, Fantasy</genre>
    </FilmyData>
    <FilmyData>
        <title>Star Wars: Episode III - Revenge of the Sith</title>
        <filmImage>starwars3</filmImage>
        <director>George Lucas</director>
        <writers>George Lucas</writers>
        <cast>Hayden Christensen, Ewan McGregor, Natalie Portman, Ian McDiarmid, Samuel L. Jackson,
            Jimmy Smits, Frank Oz
        </cast>
        <language>English</language>
        <country>USA</country>
        <plot>The evil Darth Sidious enacts his final plan for unlimited power—and the heroic Jedi
            Anakin Skywalker must choose a side.
        </plot>
        <genre>Action, Adventure, Fantasy</genre>
    </FilmyData>
    <FilmyData>
        <title>Transformers</title>
        <filmImage>transformers1</filmImage>
        <director>Michael Bay</director>
        <writers>Alex Kurtzman, Roberto Orci, John Rogers</writers>
        <cast>Shia LaBeouf, Megan Fox, Josh Duhamel, Tyrese Gibson, Rachael Taylor, John Turturro,
            Peter Cullen
        </cast>
        <language>English</language>
        <country>USA</country>
        <plot>Young teenager Sam Witwicky becomes involved in the ancient struggle between two
            extraterrestrial factions of transforming robots—the heroic Autobots and the evil
            Decepticons. Sam holds the clue to unimaginable power and the Decepticons will stop at
            nothing to retrieve it.
        </plot>
        <genre>Action, Adventure, Sci-Fi</genre>
    </FilmyData>
    <FilmyData>
        <title>Iron Man</title>
        <filmImage>ironmam1</filmImage>
        <director>Jon Favreau</director>
        <writers>Mark Fergus, Hawk Ostby, Art Marcum, Matt Holloway</writers>
        <cast>Robert Downey Jr., Gwyneth Paltrow, Terrence Howard, Jeff Bridges</cast>
        <language>English</language>
        <country>USA</country>
        <plot>After being held captive in an Afghan cave, billionaire engineer Tony Stark creates a
            unique weaponized suit of armor to fight against evil forces and becomes the superhero
            Iron Man.
        </plot>
        <genre>Action, Adventure, Sci-Fi</genre>
    </FilmyData>
    <FilmyData>
        <title>Star Wars: Episode IV - A New Hope</title>
        <filmImage>starwars4</filmImage>
        <director>George Lucas</director>
        <writers>George Lucas</writers>
        <cast>Mark Hamill, Harrison Ford, Carrie Fisher, Alec Guinness</cast>
        <language>English</language>
        <country>USA</country>
        <plot>Luke Skywalker joins forces with a Jedi Knight, a cocky pilot, a Wookiee, and two
            droids to save the galaxy from the Empire's world-destroying battle station, while also
            attempting to rescue Princess Leia from the mysterious Darth Vader.
        </plot>
        <genre>Action, Adventure, Fantasy</genre>
    </FilmyData>
    <FilmyData>
        <title>Toy Story</title>
        <filmImage>toystory1</filmImage>
        <director>John Lasseter</director>
        <writers>John Lasseter, Pete Docter, Andrew Stanton, Joe Ranft, Joss Whedon</writers>
        <cast>Tom Hanks, Tim Allen, Don Rickles, Jim Varney</cast>
        <language>English</language>
        <country>USA</country>
        <plot>A cowboy doll is profoundly threatened and jealous when a new spaceman figure
            supplants him as top toy in a boy's room.
        </plot>
        <genre>Animation, Adventure, Comedy</genre>
    </FilmyData>
    <FilmyData>
        <title>The Avengers</title>
        <filmImage>avengers</filmImage>
        <director>Joss Whedon</director>
        <writers>Joss Whedon, Zak Penn</writers>
        <cast>Robert Downey Jr., Chris Evans, Mark Ruffalo, Chris Hemsworth, Scarlett Johansson,
            Jeremy Renner
        </cast>
        <language>English</language>
        <country>USA</country>
        <plot>Earth's mightiest heroes must come together and learn to fight as a team to stop the
            mischievous Loki and his alien army from enslaving humanity.
        </plot>
        <genre>Action, Adventure, Sci-Fi</genre>
    </FilmyData>
    <FilmyData>
        <title>Indiana Jones: Raiders of the Lost Ark</title>
        <filmImage>indianajohneslostark</filmImage>
        <director>Steven Spielberg</director>
        <writers>Lawrence Kasdan</writers>
        <cast>Harrison Ford, Karen Allen, Paul Freeman</cast>
        <language>English</language>
        <country>USA</country>
        <plot>Archaeologist and adventurer Indiana Jones is hired by the U.S. government to find the
            Ark of the Covenant before the Nazis.
        </plot>
        <genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
    </FilmyData>
    <FilmyData>
        <title>Finding Nemo</title>
        <filmImage>findingnemo</filmImage>
        <director>Andrew Stanton, Lee Unkrich</director>
        <writers>Andrew Stanton, Bob Peterson, David Reynolds</writers>
        <cast>Albert Brooks, Ellen DeGeneres, Alexander Gould</cast>
        <language>English</language>
        <country>USA</country>
        <plot>After his son is captured in the Great Barrier Reef and taken to Sydney, a timid
            clownfish sets out on a journey to bring him home.
        </plot>
        <genre>Animation, Adventure, Comedy</genre>
    </FilmyData>
    <FilmyData>
        <title>Spider-Man: Homecoming</title>
        <filmImage>spidermanhomecoming</filmImage>
        <director>Jon Watts</director>
        <writers>Jonathan Goldstein, John Francis Daley, Jon Watts, Christopher Ford, Chris McKenna,
            Erik Sommers
        </writers>
        <cast>Tom Holland, Michael Keaton, Robert Downey Jr., Marisa Tomei</cast>
        <language>English</language>
        <country>USA</country>
        <plot>Peter Parker balances his life as an ordinary high school student in Queens with his
            superhero alter-ego Spider-Man, and finds himself on the trail of a new menace prowling
            the skies of New York City.
        </plot>
        <genre>Action, Adventure, Sci-Fi</genre>
    </FilmyData>
    <FilmyData>
        <title>Star Wars: Episode VI - Return of the Jedi</title>
        <filmImage>starwars6</filmImage>
        <director>Richard Marquand</director>
        <writers>Lawrence Kasdan, George Lucas</writers>
        <cast>Mark Hamill, Harrison Ford, Carrie Fisher, Billy Dee Williams</cast>
        <language>English</language>
        <country>USA</country>
        <plot>After a daring mission to rescue Han Solo from Jabba the Hutt, the Rebels dispatch to
            Endor to destroy the second Death Star. Meanwhile, Luke Skywalker struggles to bring
            Darth Vader back to the light side of the Force.
        </plot>
        <genre>Action, Adventure, Fantasy</genre>
    </FilmyData>
    <FilmyData>
        <title>Frozen</title>
        <filmImage>frozen</filmImage>
        <director>Chris Buck, Jennifer Lee</director>
        <writers>Jennifer Lee, Chris Buck, Shane Morris</writers>
        <cast>Kristen Bell, Idina Menzel, Jonathan Groff, Josh Gad</cast>
        <language>English</language>
        <country>USA</country>
        <plot>When the newly crowned Queen Elsa accidentally uses her power to turn things into ice
            to curse her home in infinite winter, her sister Anna teams up with a mountain man, his
            playful reindeer, and a snowman to change the weather condition.
        </plot>
        <genre>Animation, Adventure, Comedy</genre>
    </FilmyData>
    <FilmyData>
        <title>Guardians of the Galaxy</title>
        <filmImage>guardiansofthegalaxy</filmImage>
        <director>James Gunn</director>
        <writers>James Gunn, Nicole Perlman</writers>
        <cast>Chris Pratt, Zoe Saldana, Dave Bautista, Vin Diesel, Bradley Cooper</cast>
        <language>English</language>
        <country>USA</country>
        <plot>A group of intergalactic criminals is forced to work together to stop a fanatical
            warrior from taking control of the universe.
        </plot>
        <genre>Action, Adventure, Comedy</genre>
    </FilmyData>
    <FilmyData>
        <title>Avengers: Infinity War</title>
        <filmImage>avengersinfinitywar</filmImage>
        <director>Anthony Russo, Joe Russo</director>
        <writers>Christopher Markus, Stephen McFeely</writers>
        <cast>Robert Downey Jr., Chris Hemsworth, Mark Ruffalo, Chris Evans, Scarlett Johansson
        </cast>
        <language>English</language>
        <country>USA</country>
        <plot>The Avengers and their allies must be willing to sacrifice all in an attempt to defeat
            the powerful Thanos before his blitz of devastation and ruin puts an end to the
            universe.
        </plot>
        <genre>Action, Adventure, Fantasy</genre>
    </FilmyData>
    <FilmyData>
        <title>Star Wars: Episode V - The Empire Strikes Back</title>
        <filmImage>starwars5</filmImage>
        <director>Irvin Kershner</director>
        <writers>Leigh Brackett, Lawrence Kasdan, George Lucas</writers>
        <cast>Mark Hamill, Harrison Ford, Carrie Fisher, Billy Dee Williams</cast>
        <language>English</language>
        <country>USA</country>
        <plot>After the rebels are overpowered by the Empire on the ice planet Hoth, Luke Skywalker
            begins Jedi training with Yoda, while his friends are pursued by Darth Vader.
        </plot>
        <genre>Action, Adventure, Fantasy</genre>
    </FilmyData>
    <FilmyData>
        <title>Thor: Ragnarok</title>
        <filmImage>thorragnarok</filmImage>
        <director>Taika Waititi</director>
        <writers>Eric Pearson, Craig Kyle, Christopher L. Yost</writers>
        <cast>Chris Hemsworth, Tom Hiddleston, Cate Blanchett, Mark Ruffalo</cast>
        <language>English</language>
        <country>USA</country>
        <plot>Imprisoned on the planet Sakaar, Thor must race against time to return to Asgard and
            stop Ragnarok, the destruction of his world, at the hands of the powerful and ruthless
            villain Hela.
        </plot>
        <genre>Action, Adventure, Comedy</genre>
    </FilmyData>

    <FilmyData>
        <title>Avengers: Endgame</title>
        <filmImage>avengersendgame</filmImage>
        <director>Anthony Russo, Joe Russo</director>
        <writers>Christopher Markus, Stephen McFeely</writers>
        <cast>Robert Downey Jr., Chris Evans, Mark Ruffalo, Chris Hemsworth, Scarlett Johansson
        </cast>
        <language>English</language>
        <country>USA</country>
        <plot>After the devastating events of Avengers: Infinity War, the universe is in ruins. With
            the help of remaining allies, the Avengers assemble once more in order to reverse
            Thanos' actions and restore balance to the universe.
        </plot>
        <genre>Action, Adventure, Drama</genre>
    </FilmyData>
</filmyDataList>